<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post on wonderland</title>
    <link>http://example.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post on wonderland</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Theme by David Yates. Text and illustrations from Project Gutenburg.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 20:16:18 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Shortcodes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2019/05/07/custom-shortcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 20:16:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2019/05/07/custom-shortcodes/</guid>
      <description>Allover comes with a couple of shortcodes that I find quite useful, and perhaps you will too.
Captions Markdown-capable image captions, for if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to use {{&amp;lt; figure &amp;gt;}}:
This is a caption. It can contain markdown. However, it&amp;rsquo;s forced italic through CSS.
Because captions are independent of what they&amp;rsquo;re captions, you can use them for codeblocks, video embeds, and anything else you want, not just images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2019/05/07/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 20:08:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2019/05/07/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: The Rabbit Sends in a Little Bill</title>
      <link>http://example.org/1862/07/07/ch4-the-rabbit-sends-in-a-little-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 1862 19:33:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/1862/07/07/ch4-the-rabbit-sends-in-a-little-bill/</guid>
      <description>It was the White Rabbit, trotting slowly back again and looking anxiously about as it went, as if it had lost something; Alice heard it muttering to itself, &amp;ldquo;The Duchess! The Duchess! Oh, my dear paws! Oh, my fur and whiskers! She&amp;rsquo;ll get me executed, as sure as ferrets are ferrets! Where can I have dropped them, I wonder?&amp;rdquo; Alice guessed in a moment that it was looking for the fan and the pair of white kid-gloves and she very good-naturedly began hunting about for them, but they were nowhere to be seen&amp;ndash;everything seemed to have changed since her swim in the pool, and the great hall, with the glass table and the little door, had vanished completely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: A Caucus-Race and a Long Tale</title>
      <link>http://example.org/1862/07/06/ch3-a-caucus-race-and-a-long-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 1862 19:33:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/1862/07/06/ch3-a-caucus-race-and-a-long-tale/</guid>
      <description>They were indeed a queer-looking party that assembled on the bank&amp;ndash;the birds with draggled feathers, the animals with their fur clinging close to them, and all dripping wet, cross and uncomfortable.
The first question, of course, was how to get dry again. They had a consultation about this and after a few minutes, it seemed quite natural to Alice to find herself talking familiarly with them, as if she had known them all her life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: The Pool of Tears</title>
      <link>http://example.org/1862/07/05/ch2-the-pool-of-tears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 1862 19:33:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/1862/07/05/ch2-the-pool-of-tears/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Curiouser and curiouser!&amp;rdquo; cried Alice (she was so much surprised that for the moment she quite forgot how to speak good English). &amp;ldquo;Now I&amp;rsquo;m opening out like the largest telescope that ever was! Good-by, feet! Oh, my poor little feet, I wonder who will put on your shoes and stockings for you now, dears? I shall be a great deal too far off to trouble myself about you.&amp;rdquo;
Just at this moment her head struck against the roof of the hall; in fact, she was now rather more than nine feet high, and she at once took up the little golden key and hurried off to the garden door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: Down the Rabbit-Hole</title>
      <link>http://example.org/1862/07/04/ch1-down-the-rabbit-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 1862 19:33:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/1862/07/04/ch1-down-the-rabbit-hole/</guid>
      <description>Alice was beginning to get very tired of sitting by her sister on the bank, and of having nothing to do. Once or twice she had peeped into the book her sister was reading, but it had no pictures or conversations in it, &amp;ldquo;and what is the use of a book,&amp;rdquo; thought Alice, &amp;ldquo;without pictures or conversations?&amp;rdquo;
So she was considering in her own mind (as well as she could, for the day made her feel very sleepy and stupid), whether the pleasure of making a daisy-chain would be worth the trouble of getting up and picking the daisies, when suddenly a White Rabbit with pink eyes ran close by her.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>